The Amanda Seal Show of the week is, what is your opinion on polyamorous relationships?
Absolutely not.
Why not?
One of one, one of none.
Not sharing.
Final answer.
I'm married.
So my answer has to be, you know, 100% spot on.
So I'm going to say no to the polyamorousness.
In a previous lifetime, I could have, I mean, I could have easily had a harem or two.
I feel like I get jealous real quick.
Like, I feel like, never mind, I'm not going to say what I was going to say.
But I feel like I get jealous real quick.
Polyamorous is like, for the old heads who need to spice up, they married.
And this is where people get messed up.
Forever is such a long time.
And then it's like, when it comes to cheating, it's like, yeah, you shouldn't cheat on your partner.
But that's why you go polyamorous.
Because it's like, if there's a mutual understanding, then everyone can just have fun.
Like, life is too short to be out here just being cuffed up and s***.
Don't ask me no questions.
No, I'm not sharing you.
Yeah, I ain't allowing that, man.
I'm not going out there and getting somebody else.
And, yeah, I expect my other significant other to do the same thing.
A polyamorous, especially a man, a man does not really want that.
We want to say, we want the woman to accept that.
But we're not going to accept that from a woman.
We are, we are, we are.